Yuki-chan, long time no see.
ゆきちゃん、久々
It's been a while.
久々です
picture?
え?
Yuki-chan, what are you doing to take care of your glasses?
ゆきちゃん何、メガネケアしてんの?
A little makeover today.
今日はちょっとイメチェン
The atmosphere has changed a bit.
ちょっと雰囲気変わったね
I got a makeover.
イメチェンしました
Liar, did you get a makeover?
うそ、イメチェンしたの?
I got a makeover.
イメチェンしました
cute.
かわいい
She's starting to look like a pretty older sister.
ちょっとなんか綺麗なお姉さんみたいな感じになってきたじゃん
However, I started to feel like a beautiful older sister.
だけどさ、綺麗なお姉さんみたいな感じになってきたの、
Only in the morning.
朝あれだけどさ
Yeah.
うん
Are you still wearing it?
まだつけてんの?
What?
何を?
picture?
え?
Yes, hmm.
はい、うーんして
Hmm.
うーんって
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
It will be updated when this disappears.
これ消えたら更新されてくる
Are you still wearing it?
まだつけてんの?
It will be updated when this disappears.
これ消えたら更新されてくる
It's not popular.
流行んないよ
It's not popular anymore.
流行んないよ、もうそれ
It's not popular anymore, it's not popular anymore,
もう流行んないんだけど、 流行んないんだけど、
It will be updated automatically.
勝手に更新されちゃう
Will it be updated automatically?
勝手に更新されちゃうの?
lie?
うそ?
I see.
そっか
I'm just feeling, uh, a little bit today.
ちょっとさ、今日はさ、 うーんって感じなんだけどさ
Do you feel like hmmm?
うーんって感じ?
yes.
そう
Are you interested in 3P?
3Pとか興味ある?
I don't know because I've never done it.
したことないからわかんない
I've never done it.
したことない
Well, that's true.
まあそうだよね
Well, when we meet for the first time, the number of experienced people will increase rapidly.
まあさ、初めて会った時にさ、経験人数どんどん増やしていくよ
I think I conveyed that to you.
っていう のはさ、伝えたと思うんだよね
Well, maybe it was during the cold season, or during the winter.
まああれ、寒かった時期か、冬の時期か
So, I've been updating it gradually.
で、徐々に徐々にさ、更新してきてんじゃん
gradually?
徐々に?
Gradually gradually.
徐々に徐々に
You no longer have one hand.
片手じゃなくなってきたでしょ
So, just like that, more
だからさ、そういうので、もっとね、
Next time I'm going to aim for both hands,
今度両手目指していこうっていうので、
It's not just about making a few bucks though.
ちょっと数稼ぎじゃないけどさ
Two people at once?
一気に2人?
yes.
そう
It looks like two people will be updating,
2人更新しちゃいますみたいな感じなんだけど、
good?
いい?
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
It's kind of okay.
まあまあまあみたいな
OK、OK
You're so cute today too, Yuki-chan.
かわいいね、今日もね、ゆきちゃんね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I agree.
そうだね
Well then, okay, can I just say that I've got one more shot?
じゃあそしたらさ、まあさ、あともう1個ぶっこんだ言っていい?
Did you blow it?
ぶっこんだ?
Yeah.
うん
Among those threesomes, are you interested in being a virgin today?
その3Pの中でもさ、今日はさ、童貞って興味ある?
What about virginity?
童貞は?
That's a real virgin.
あの、ガチ童貞
Really virgin?
ガチ童貞?
Yeah.
うん
My uncle, just a little bit, uh...
おじさんがさ、ちょっとさ、あの、
You drew a hat, right?
帽子を書きたんだよね
What do you think of the actor?
男優さんどうですか?
Like.
みたいな
Hey.
へー
Then, more than I expected, I heard someone say, ``I want to become an actor.''
したらさ、まあ思いの他さ、男優やりたいですっていう声がさ、
I've come a long way, to my uncle's place.
かなり来てさ、おじさんのところに
So, among them, select carefully and include virgins?
で、 その中で厳選して、 童貞も?
yes.
そう
Carefully selected virgins too?
厳選した童貞も?
yes.
そう
Just a little bit, um, because I picked it up.
っていうのをちょっとね、あの、拾ってきたからさ
I picked it up because I just found it.
拾ってきたっていうかさ、ちょっと見つけてきたからさ
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
yes.
そう
A virgin plus a bit of an actor.
童貞プラス、ちょっと男優さん
It's like a 3P.
3Pでみたいな感じで
It's so fresh.
すごい新鮮ですね
Have you ever been a virgin?
童貞やったことある?
No, no, no.
ないないない
Isn't it?
ないでしょ?
No virginity, no threesome.
童貞もない、3Pもない
That's right.
だよね
I see, so that's it, I thought I'd do it today.
そっか、じゃあまあそれでさ、ちょっと今日やっていこうかなと思
Yes, but.
うん だけど
From now on, you're a virgin,
これからさ、ちょっとさ、童貞の人さ、
I'll come pick you up in a bit.
ちょっと迎えに行くからさ
How old do you think she is a virgin?
何歳の童貞だと思う?
There are many people who are virgins.
いるじゃんよく、童貞の人ってさ
40 years old, 30 years old, 20 years old.
40歳、30歳、20歳
At what age should you be in the shared range?
何歳くらいだったら共用範囲?
How old were you? In your 20s.
何歳くらいだったら、20代
20th generation?
20代?
Do you hate being a virgin in your 30s or 40s?
30代、40代の童貞は嫌だ?
Oh, I don't know.
え、わかんない
I don't like it.
嫌だよね
It's okay, I'm in my 20s.
大丈夫です、20代です
noisily.
じゃあじゃあ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
OK
Yuki-chan, there's a little swing.
ゆきちゃん、ちょっとブランコあるしさ、
Let's go on a swing for a while.
ちょっとブランコ乗ろうよ
What if I ride?
乗ると?
I feel more like an adult now.
なんか大人っぽくなったね
Yeah, but I also wear clothes like this.
え、でもこういう服も着ますよ
lie?
嘘?
Uncle, I miss you a little.
おじさん、ちょっと寂しいわ
picture?
え?
Uncle, I miss you a little.
おじさん、ちょっと寂しいわ
why?
なんで?
Yuki-chan looks a little more mature,
ちょっと大人っぽくなっているゆきちゃん、
I miss you.
寂しいわ
I've always worn clothes like this.
元々こういう服着るんだってわ
Is that so?
そうなの?
fun?
楽しい?
Swing.
ブランコ
First swing in years.
何年ぶりのブランコ
How many years has it been since?
何年ぶり?
lie?
嘘?
what?
何?
Are you hiding it?
隠してる?
that.
それ
this?
これ?
I'm hiding it.
隠してる
Please open it again.
もうちょっとまた開いて
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
I can't see anything.
何も見えません
That's right.
それそうだ
This looks like a skirt, but it's actually pants.
これスカートに見えてなんかパンツだし
I can't see anything.
何も見えません
Peel off something so erotic.
そこまでエロいものをはがす
Eh, Yuki-chan?
え、とかさ、ゆきちゃんか
It's because of the clothes.
その服だからっていう
My boobs have gotten bigger.
なんかおっぱい大きくなったな
It's gotten bigger, hasn't it?
大きくなったよね
I went up 1 cup though.
1カップはあがったけど
lie?
嘘?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Because there's no one there.
誰もいないから
I definitely don't understand brushes.
ブラシが絶対わかんないわ
Take a look.
めくってみてよ
What?
何を?
From below.
下から
this?
これ?
like this?
こう?
It's cold.
寒いって
It's cold because it's outside.
外だから寒いって
A moment, a moment.
一瞬、一瞬
Hey.
ほい
What's in style today?
何 今日のスタイリー?
Isn't it cute?
可愛くない?
He's cute today.
今日は可愛いやつ
Because she dresses like an adult.
服装が大人っぽいから
The one inside is cute.
中 は可愛いやつ
Come a little closer.
もうちょっと寄ってよ
Can you come a little closer?
もうちょっと寄って?
cold.
寒い
I guess it's gotten a little bigger after all.
やっぱりちょっと大きくなったのかね
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
I feel a little less shy now.
ちょっと恥じらいもなくなってきたね、
gradually.
だんだん
Embarrassing?
恥ずい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing because it's outside.
さすがに外だから恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Shall I try it next time?
今度嫌がやってみる?
I absolutely hate it.
絶対嫌
why?
なんで?
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
lie?
嘘?
I absolutely hate it.
絶対嫌だ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいって
It's embarrassing. What should I say?
恥ずかしいことをさ、ちょっと、何て言うの?
Let's make a lot with Usan.
いっぱいうさんと作っていこうよ
Embarrassing memories.
恥ずかしい思い出を
Even 3P is embarrassing.
3Pでも恥ずかしいのに
Right?
でしょ?
So let's make more and more embarrassing memories.
だからもっともっと恥ずかしい思い出いっぱい作っていこうよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Aren't you happy?
嬉しくない?
I'm not happy.
嬉しくないよ
嬉しくない
Would you like some glasses?
ちょっとメガネなんかいい?
lie?
嘘?
Just like an erotic teacher, move your glasses,
ちょっとエロ教師みたいにさ、メガネずらしてさ、
Try looking up.
上目遣いしてみて
I don't know how to look up.
上目遣いの仕方がわからない
cute.
かわいい
It feels like Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃんって感じだね
I don't know what Yuki-chan feels like.
そのゆきちゃんって感じがわからない
cute.
かわいい
OK
So are you bored yet?
じゃあもう飽きた?
Late child.
晩子
I'm tired.
飽きた
飽きたね
Then let's go.
じゃあ行こうか
let's go.
行こう
Shall we go?
行こうか
Let's go get you.
お迎え行こう
Shall I go pick you up?
お迎え行こうか
Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん
You're probably saying that's it.
多分あれだよって言ってるでしょ
Is Acchan better?
あっちゃんの方が?
You're probably saying that's it.
多分あれだよって言ってるでしょ
Is Acchan better?
あっちゃんの方が?
yes.
そう
Shall we go?
行こうか
I'll go.
行ってみます
let's go.
行こう
Hello.
こんにちは
nice to meet you.
初めまして
Eh, what's your name?
え、お名前は?
Well, I'm Makoto Tanabe.
えっと、田辺誠です
Makoto Tanabe.
田辺誠
I'm glad it's not your full name.
フルネームじゃなくてよかったね
I see.
そっか
Mr. Makoto Tanabe.
田辺誠さん
Oh, uh, that's what you applied for, right?
え、あの、応募してきたの、あれですよね
yes.
はい
Um, what do you say?
あの、何て言うんだろう
Are you sure it's a serious feeling?
ガチドーテっていう感じで、間違いないですか?
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
REASONS
OKOK
Actually, this is what girls look like.
実際にじゃあ、ちょっと、女の子こんな感じだけど
What do you think?
どう、どうですか?
感想は?
cute.
かわいい
You don't think so.
思ってないでしょ
cute.
かわいい
nice.
いいね
copper?
どう?
What?
何が?
get nervous?
緊張する?
I could feel the tension.
緊張が映ってきた
It has appeared.
映ってきた
That's right.
そうだよね
OK
Well then, let's go to a hotel then.
じゃあ、まぁ、ホテル行こうか、そしたら
I got it.
了解です
copper?
どう?
What do you mean?
どうって何が?
Hotel.
ホテル
Today is different from usual,
今日はいつもの、いつもとさ、違う、
I tried to take pictures of a business hotel, not a love hotel.
ラブホテルじゃなくて、ビジネスホテルをちゃんと撮ってみました
But.
けど
Is it okay to do something like this once in a while?
た まにはこういうのもいい?
Yeah.
うん
It's beautiful.
きれいね
beautiful?
きれい?
It's beautiful.
きれいね
Really?
本当に?
So, Tanabe-san, would you mind?
じゃあ、ちょっと田辺さん、いいすか?
I think I'll ask Mr. Tanabe some questions.
ちょっと田辺さんに色々質問していこうかなと思うからさ
Yeah.
うん
I'd like Yuki-chan to ask me some questions too.
ゆきちゃんからも質問してあげてほしいんだけどさ
Do I have a question?
私から質問?
High hurdle.
ハードル高
So, please sit down for a moment.
じゃあ、ちょっと座ってもらって
To the side.
横に
Can you please come over here a little longer?
もうちょっとこっちに来てもらっていいすか?
Well then, let's talk about Yuki-chan for a little while.
じゃあ、ゆきちゃんももうちょっと
I?
私が?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Shall I go by your side?
私がそばに行くけ?
yes.
はい
Well then, Mr. Tanabe, nice to meet you again.
じゃあ、田辺さん、改めまして
Mr. Tanabe said that at the beginning, but...
田辺さんはさ、冒頭でもさ、だけど、
There's no doubt that it's a torso.
胴手で間違いないんだよね
yes.
はい
Because, Yuki-chan.
だってよ、ゆきちゃん
Because.
だってよ
Well, Mr. Tanabe, I don't see any girls, but...
なかなかさ、田辺さん、女の子見ないけどさ、
What should we do, Yuki-chan?
どうすか、ゆきちゃんは?
What do you think?
どう す か?
Just take a look.
ちょっと見てみてよ
copper?
どう?
A little closer.
ちょっと近くに
I'm next to you, what should I do?
隣にいるけど、どうすか?
Because I'm nervous.
緊張してるから
cute?
かわいい?
type?
タイプ?
yes.
はい
What kind of girl is Tanabe-san's type?
どういう子が田辺さんタイプなの?
I'm nervous and I feel like I'm in a panic.
緊張して、てんてんてんまるみたいな感じか
So, what kind of play do you like?
じゃあ、どういうプレーが好きなんですか?
Is there something you would like to try playing like this?
こういうプレーしてみたいなとかっていうのあんの?
Yuki-chan is so cute.
ゆきちゃん、かわいい
Hello.
どうもー
It's like Tenten Tenmaru.
てんてんてんまるみたいなね
I don't really understand.
やっぱ分かんないよね
yes.
はい
I see.
そっか
Well, today I have Mr. Tanabe as my teacher.
じゃあ、今日はね、田辺さんの先生がいるんで
With my teacher, I graduated from my virginity with an assistant.
先生とともに、アシスタントありの童貞卒業っていうのを、
For Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃんにね
I thought maybe Yuki-chan and I would do it together.
ゆきちゃんと一緒にやってもらおうかなって
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Close hands and butts.
近手とお尻派
Butt fan?
お尻派?
Take it, Yuki-chan.
取ってよ、ゆきちゃん
It's impossible.
無理です
I'm not confident.
自信ないです
自信ないって
I don't have confidence in my butt.
お尻は自信ないです
It's okay, Yuki-chan.
大丈夫で、ゆきちゃん
Because it's beautiful.
きれいだから
Hello.
どうもー
Yuki-chan, you've lost some weight.
ゆきちゃん、ちょっとさ、痩せたね
Eh, right?
えっ、でしょ?
Skin is smooth.
肌つやい
No, no.
違う違う
I want you to see a thinner person.
痩せた方を見てほしい
How can I see it?
どうやって見ればいい?
I can only see my feet.
足しか見えないけど
I'll take it off anyway.
どうせ脱ぐもん
I agree.
そうだね
So, did you say you've ever chewed?
じゃあ さ、チューしたことあるって言ったっけ?
There's no chew?
チューもないんだっけ?
do not have.
ない
There's no chew either.
チューもないんだ
So it's the first time I've had sex,
じゃあ初中初セックスっていうことで、
We have prepared the most beautiful women for you,
最高の美女を用意させていただきましたんで、
Please enjoy it to your heart's content.
思う存分楽しんでください
Is that okay, Mr. Tanabe?
いい ですか、たなべさん
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Is that okay?
っていうことなので、いい?
I will do my best.
頑張ります
do my best?
頑張る?
Will you do your best?
頑張ってくれる?
I'm not trying too hard though.
頑張るもんじゃないけどね
good?
いい?
Well then, Tanabe-san, wait a moment.
じゃあまずさ、たなべさんさ、 ちょっとじゃあ、
Shall I take off my clothes?
服脱がせてみようか
It's a woman, Yuki-chan, let's take her clothes off.
女性のさ、ゆきちゃんのさ、服脱がせてみようよ
clothes.
洋服
It's okay.
いいっすよ
That's good.
いい っすよ
Should I peel it?
むいたほうがいい?
Is it okay to leave it like this?
このままでいい?
Peel it, peel it.
むいてあげて、むいてあげて
It's swollen.
むくんじゃん
It is better to peel it off.
むいてあげたほうがいいっていうのが、
It was a little like that.
ちょっとあれだった
How do you know?
なんでわかるでしょ
Sorry, sorry.
ごめんごめん
No, you can take off your clothes.
いや、服脱がしてあげていいよ
Please do as you wish.
思うがままにやってあげてください
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Is Yuki-chan embarrassed?
ゆきちゃん恥ずかしい?
I heard it.
聞こえちゃった
That's fine, that's fine.
いいじゃん、それがいいんじゃん
He seems like a complete renouncer.
ガチの同棄さんのようだって
I know, I know.
わかってるわかってる
Come to think of it.
そういえばそう
When did you tie the knot?
いつこみ結んだの?
It sounds like you're very motivated.
やる気満々って感じだね
Just now, just now.
さ っき、さっき
Chau chau chau chau chau chau.
ちゃうちゃうちゃうちゃうちゃうちゃう
No.
だめ
Don't hide it for a second.
ちょっと隠さないで
Tanabi-san, what should we do then?
たなびさん、じゃあ、どうすか?
Yuki-chan's naked body.
ゆきちゃんの裸は
You're not naked, are you?
裸じゃないでしょ
I'm not naked.
裸じゃないです
What do you think of the finished look?
仕上げ姿はどうすか?
What should I do?
どうすか?
What do you think?
感想はどうすか?
Ah, that's good.
あ、それがいい
Wait a minute, then try touching it.
ちょっと、じゃあ、触ってみる
Tsun, try tsun.
ツン、ツンしてみる
Wait a minute, then let's try it.
ちょっと、じゃあ、ツン、ツンしてみよう
Just give it a try.
ちょっと、ツン、ツンしてみて
Where, where, where?
どこ、どこ、どこ?
chest.
胸
Just a little tsun, tsun.
ちょっと、ツン、ツンって
This is your first time touching it.
初めて、初めて触れるんでしょ
yes.
はい
Tsun, tsun, then, let's try it.
ツン、ツンって、じゃあ、ちょっとしてみようか
Probably not there.
たぶんね、そこじゃないでしょ
Not there, definitely.
そこじゃない、絶対
Not there, but the cleavage?
そこじゃなくて、谷間?
yes.
はい
copper?
どう?
What do you think?
どうですか?
soft.
柔らかい
copper?
どう?
happy?
嬉しい?
yes.
はい
Can I have you do it manually?
ちょっと手動かしてもらっていいですか?
I don't know.
わかんねぇか
Let's try removing the bottom next time.
今度、下を抜かしてみようか
Oh, be polite.
あら、ご丁寧に
thank you.
ありがとうございます